<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Upcoming &amp; Past Events on Breaking the Silos</title>
    <link>https://breakingthesilos.be/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Upcoming &amp; Past Events on Breaking the Silos</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 16:11:42 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://breakingthesilos.be/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Breaking the Silos: Hybrid &amp; Remote Work</title>
      <link></link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 16:11:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid></guid>
      <description>Our second meetup features several use cases from Belgian tech companies, followed by a panel discussion on hybrid and remote work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breaking the Silos: Neurodiversity</title>
      <link></link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 15:24:52 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid></guid>
      <description>Our first meetup focuses on Neurodiversity (ADHD, ASD, intellectual giftedness, etc.), featuring three live keynote speakers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About the Initiative</title>
      <link>https://breakingthesilos.be/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breakingthesilos.be/about/</guid>
      <description>Breaking the Silos is all about breaking siloed thinking and approaches within Belgian tech companies, and improving collaboration by:
enlightening companies to choose sustainable solutions for problems over short-term fixes inspiring companies to embrace change in their market and in society as a whole building a safe and inclusive work environment for all people involved showcasing the advantages and success stories of breaking siloed thinking. We build a community of like-minded organisations, leaders and people that want to make sustainable change happen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>https://breakingthesilos.be/code-of-conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breakingthesilos.be/code-of-conduct/</guid>
      <description>Work In Progress This code of conduct is a work in progress. Our intent is to finalise and fully start enforcing it before the first event of 2023.
We value feedback on the contents and form of the text below. Please contact an organiser if you have any suggestions or remarks. Thank you!
Regardless of the CoC below being a work in progress, if you are being harassed at one of our events, notice that someone else is being harassed, or have any other concerns, please do contact an organiser or member of event staff immediately.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Community</title>
      <link>https://breakingthesilos.be/community/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breakingthesilos.be/community/</guid>
      <description>Meetup.com To become a member and RSVP to our events, join the Breaking the Silos group on Meetup.com.
Discord server Discord is a messaging platform similar to Microsoft Teams and Slack. Since October 2022, we maintain a Discord server for chatting with members of the community.
You can join the Breaking the Silos Discord server here.
Social media You can also find and engage with us on LinkedIn, Twitter, Instagram, and YouTube.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
