<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Upcoming &amp; Past Events on Breaking the Silos</title>
    <link>https://breakingthesilos.be/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Upcoming &amp; Past Events on Breaking the Silos</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 17:06:24 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://breakingthesilos.be/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Breaking the Silos: Inclusion</title>
      <link>https://breakingthesilos.be/event/inclusion/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 17:06:24 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breakingthesilos.be/event/inclusion/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;At this meetup, we focus on inclusion in tech companies. Discover new strategies to foster diversity, equity and belonging in your organisation, hear from industry experts, and connect with like-minded individuals from the community.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breaking the Silos: Hybrid &amp; Remote Work</title>
      <link>https://breakingthesilos.be/event/hybrid-remote-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 16:11:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breakingthesilos.be/event/hybrid-remote-work/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;How have Belgian tech companies evolved to facilitate remote or hybrid work? Or have they?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the second meetup of Breaking the Silos, we’re presenting four cases of Belgian tech companies outlining their trajectory in (not) adopting hybrid &amp;amp; remote work, followed by a vivid panel discussion.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breaking the Silos: Neurodiversity</title>
      <link>https://breakingthesilos.be/event/neurodiversity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 15:24:52 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breakingthesilos.be/event/neurodiversity/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Our first meetup focuses on Neurodiversity (ADHD, ASD, intellectual giftedness, etc.), featuring four live keynote speakers.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About the Initiative</title>
      <link>https://breakingthesilos.be/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breakingthesilos.be/about/</guid>
      <description>Breaking the Silos is all about breaking siloed thinking and approaches within Belgian tech companies, and improving collaboration by:
enlightening companies to choose sustainable solutions for problems over short-term fixes inspiring companies to embrace change in their market and in society as a whole building a safe and inclusive work environment for all people involved showcasing the advantages and success stories of breaking siloed thinking. We build a community of like-minded organisations, leaders and people that want to make sustainable change happen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>https://breakingthesilos.be/code-of-conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breakingthesilos.be/code-of-conduct/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;All community members, attendees, speakers, sponsors and volunteers of &lt;em&gt;Breaking the Silos&lt;/em&gt; are required to agree with the following code of conduct.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Community</title>
      <link>https://breakingthesilos.be/community/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breakingthesilos.be/community/</guid>
      <description>Meetup.com To become a member and RSVP to our events, join the Breaking the Silos group on Meetup.com.
Discord server Members of the community can engage with each other on our Discord server. Discord is a messaging platform similar to Microsoft Teams and Slack. We also use it to share book suggestions, related insights and articles, and more.
You can join the Breaking the Silos Discord server here.
Social media You can also find and engage with us on LinkedIn, Mastodon, Instagram, and YouTube.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
