<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Events on Breaking the Silos</title>
    <link>https://breakingthesilos.be/event/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Events on Breaking the Silos</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language><atom:link href="https://breakingthesilos.be/event/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Breaking the Silos: Seeing Problems as Opportunities</title>
      <link>https://breakingthesilos.be/event/seeing-problems-as-opportunities/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 21:54:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breakingthesilos.be/event/seeing-problems-as-opportunities/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Are you mainly deterred or attracted to risk?
Do risks at work keep you up at night, or are you excited to jump into them the next working day?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In times of rapid and unexpected change, there are unexpected opportunities and possibilities, if you can see the upside of risk instead of the potential downside.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A radical open-minded, curious and courageous mindset is needed to learn and thrive in this environment.
If you are really willing to challenge yourself and change your own mindset, this is the mini-conference for you.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breaking the Silos: Psychological Safety in Tech</title>
      <link>https://breakingthesilos.be/event/psychological-safety/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 20:50:39 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breakingthesilos.be/event/psychological-safety/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Join us for an insightful exploration into Psychological Safety at our upcoming mini-conference. Designed to provide a comprehensive understanding of this critical topic, the event will feature an engaging opening keynote and three enlightening case studies presented by experts and managers who have navigated the intricacies of fostering a psychologically safe environment within the tech industry.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breaking the Silos: Inclusion in Tech</title>
      <link>https://breakingthesilos.be/event/inclusion/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 17:06:24 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breakingthesilos.be/event/inclusion/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;At this meetup, we focus on inclusion in tech companies. Discover new strategies to foster diversity, equity and belonging in your organisation, hear from industry experts, and connect with like-minded individuals from the community.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breaking the Silos: Hybrid &amp; Remote Work in Tech</title>
      <link>https://breakingthesilos.be/event/hybrid-remote-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 16:11:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breakingthesilos.be/event/hybrid-remote-work/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;How have Belgian tech companies evolved to facilitate remote or hybrid work? Or have they?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the second Breaking the Silos event, we’re presenting four cases of Belgian tech companies outlining their trajectory in (not) adopting hybrid &amp;amp; remote work, followed by a vivid panel discussion.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breaking the Silos: Neurodiversity in Tech</title>
      <link>https://breakingthesilos.be/event/neurodiversity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 15:24:52 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breakingthesilos.be/event/neurodiversity/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Our first meetup focuses on Neurodiversity (ADHD, ASD, intellectual giftedness, etc.) in tech, featuring four live keynote speakers.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
